Simon Jakobsson

- 1996-03-25
- Studievägen 11b, Linköping
- +46760171013
- in Simon Jakobsson
- github.com/Znarvl
- ② simme.jakobsson@gmail.com
- Driving License Category B

About Me -

Hey there! I'm Simon, a software engineer who's all about coding and creating cool stuff. I studied software engineering and computer science at Linköping University. At 27 years old, I'm fueled by my passion for software, especially AI and web development. In my free time, you'll usually find me diving into these areas, experimenting and discovering new things. When I'm not buried in code, I love being in nature and jamming to music, which is my favorite hobby.

Languages -

- Swedish Mothertounge
- English Professional proficient
- German Limited professional knowledge
- Spanish Limited professional knowledge

Programming Languages -

- Python
- JS/TS
- Java/Kotlin
- C
- C++
- R.

Tools and Frameworks ·

- React
- Vue
- Pandas
- Numpy
- Django
- Git
- Scikit-Learn
- Windows / Linux / MacOS

Education

Master's and Bachelor's Degree

2018 - 2023 (Civ. ing.) Software Engineering and Computer Science

Engaged in a joint Bachelor's and Master's program at Linköping University, specializing in large-scale software development.

Bachelor's Degree

2017 - 2018 **Information Systems** Lund University

Linköping University

Studied Information Systems at Lund University for a period of six months before shifting focus to Software Engineering.

Gymnasium

2012 - 2015 Social Science Program Bladins

Enrolled in the Social Science Program at Bladins with a specialized focus on International Relations. Throughout the program, I had the opportunity to study all the subjects in English

Work Experience

Jun 2023 -Summer Internship Maxar Technologies

Aug 2023

Participated in a summer internship at Maxar Technologies, gaining hands-on experience in full-stack development. Collaborated on the creation of an internal website from scratch

Summer 2017 - Garden Assistant

Nova trädgård

2021

Provided support as a Garden Assistant, actively involved in tasks such as planting, watering, and installation of water systems.

Feb 2016 -

Aug 2016

Warehouse Worker Personalcentralen Served as a Warehouse Worker, offering consulting services to multiple companies in the Malmö region, including Lantmännen and Panduro

Hobby.

Sep 2015 – Feb Face-to-Face Sales Representative

Pepperminds

Linköping University

2016

Engaged as a Face-to-Face Sales Promoting and selling monthly subscriptions for organizations such as Sightsavers and Hjärnfonden.

Extra-Curricular Activities

2022- 2023 Reception Responsible at the Computer Technology Section (STABEN)

Responsible for managing the computer technology section's reception

at Linköping University.

2020 - 2021 Board Member of the Computer Technology Linköping University

Section I actively contributed to the growth and development of the organization. I collaborated with fellow board members to implement strategic initiatives, organize events, and create a supportive environment for students during the pandemic.

2019-2020 Bandmaster of Computer Technology Band Linköping University (D-band)

I had a pivotal role in leading and motivating the band members. I effectively coordinated with organizers to ensure smooth communication and seamless collaboration to create the best possible gig.